<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WALLΞTH</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome,\n\n there was no account for you yet - so one was created. Note - this one is not secured with any password for easy use - so only use it as a hot walleth for a few beverages.</string>
    <string name="request_transaction_subtitle">Request Transaction</string>
    <string name="edit_account_subtitle">Edit Account</string>
    <string name="switch_account_subtitle">Switch Account</string>
    <string name="address_book_subtitle">Address book</string>
    <string name="transaction_subtitle">Transaction details</string>
    <string name="export_account_subtitle">Export account</string>
    <string name="request_subtitle">Request</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">close</string>
    <string name="info_text"><![CDATA[
This is a native Android <a href="http://ethereum.org">Ethereum</a> light client wallet.
<br/><br/>
It uses the in process node as ethereum light client from the <a href="https://github.com/ethereum/go-ethereum">go-ethereum</a> project.
<br/><br/>
Big shout out to <a href="https://github.com/karalabe">karalabe</a>, <a href="https://github.com/fjl">fjl</a>, <a href="https://github.com/zsfelfoldi">zsfelfoldi</a> and <a href="https://github.com/obscuren">obscuren</a> here - awesome work!
<br/><br/>
This alpha uses the <a href="http://www.rinkeby.io">rinkeby</a> testnet.
<br/><br/>
WALLΞTH is trying to be as decentralized as possible. Hence it is using a light client and not centralized pre-configured nodes. Unfortunately we cannot be fully decentralized yet.
For getting the exchange rates for (fiat) references we are querying <a href="https://www.cryptocompare.com">cryptocompare</> and to get transactions we use the great <a href="https://etherscan.io">etherscan.io</a> service. The app will work if these services are down for some reason - but you might miss some features like up to date exchange rates. As soon as it is possible to get these things in a decentralized manner we will try to use it.
<br/><br/>
Our wonderful Icon is from <a href="https://cookicons.co">Michael Cook</a>.
<br/><br/>
Be aware that this is an alpha and there will be bugs. There are also some known issues like <a href="https://github.com/ethereum/go-ethereum/issues/14367">this one</a>
 and <a href="https://github.com/ethereum/go-ethereum/issues/14340">this one</a>
<br/><br/>
The project was started by <a href="http://ligi.de">ligi</a> as this is not only needed as a wallet - but also as a building block for the <a href="http://espass.it">espass</a> project
<br/><br/>
The project is libre software (aka FOSS/free/open source) - you can find code and open issues on the <a href="https://github.com/walleth">WALLΞTH GitHub Organisation</a>
<br/><br/>
Please have a great time with this app and we are happy about feedback, donations, pull-requests ..-)
<br/><br/>
The ideal place for feedback is our sub-reddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/walleth">https://www.reddit.com/r/walleth</a>
You can find the source <a href="https://github.com/walleth">on github</a>
]]></string>
    <string name="qr_code">QR-Code</string>
    <string name="text_extract_funds">You can use this QR-Code to request a transaction:</string>
    <string name="import_json_title">Import Account</string>
    <string name="request_hint"><![CDATA[
You might share this address with the hashtag <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23walleth">#walleth</a> on social media to get test ether.
<br/><a href="http://ligi.de">LIGI</a> will monitor twitter and has some test-ether collected since the launch of <a href="http://www.rinkeby.io">rinkeby</a>.
<br/>Also you can pass on the test ether you got to users you see using this hashtag and exercise transactions this way.
]]>
</string>
    <array name="day_night">
        <item>Day</item>
        <item>Night</item>
        <item>Auto</item>
    </array>

    <string name="day_or_night">Day or Night</string>
    <string name="day_or_night_summary">There is a light and a dark theme</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_success">Success</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_error">Error</string>

    <string name="select_fiat_reference">Select (Fiat) Reference</string>
    <string name="create_account_subtitle">Create Account</string>
    <string name="open_in_etherscan">Open in EtherScan</string>
    <string name="empty_view">This account was just created for you Hence it has no transactions/value yet You could now press the green button to send value to this account Or import an existing account You can find functions like these in the drawer to your left</string>
    <string name="transaction_to_label">To:</string>
    <string name="transaction_from_label">From:</string>
</resources>
